Privacy Policy
--------------

G.SKILL is committed to protecting your personal data and your privacy when visiting our website. So we have written this Privacy Policy ("Policy") to describe how we collect, share, and use personal information about you, and how you can exercise your privacy rights.

This Privacy Policy only applies to personal information that we collect through our website at www.gskill.com and our forum at www.gskill.us. In this Privacy Policy, "we", "us", and "our" refers to G.SKILL.

### Consent

G.SKILL reserves the right to amend the terms of the Policy at any time, and by using our website or forum, you hereby consent to this current Privacy Policy and agree to its terms and any future terms changes.

### Errors on our Website

Prices and availability of products are subject to change without notice. Errors will be corrected where and when discovered. G.SKILL reserves the right to revoke any stated offer, cancel orders, and to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions in any stated offer or price, including after an order has been submitted and whether or not the order has been confirmed and your payment processed.

### Information We Collect and How We Use Your Information

We collect information that you voluntarily provide to us, such as when requesting an RMA, seek technical support, or sign up for our membership program. We use the information we collect in various ways, including but not limited to:

* Provide support or services offered by G.SKILL and our affiliates
* Provide, operate, and maintain our website
* Improve, personalize, and expand our website
* Transfer your information outside Europe and the United States
* Understand and analyze how you use our website
* Develop new products, services, features, and functionality
* Communicate with you, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website or membership services, and for marketing and promotional purposes
* Find and prevent fraud

### RMA and Technical Support

When requesting RMA or technical support, we may ask for your first name, last name, shipping address, country or region, telephone number, email address, product information, and system information in order for us to process the RMA and to provide RMA or technical support related services.

### Membership Registration

When you register for our membership, you must provide your first name, last name, user name, country or region, and email address to facilitate and improve your use of the website and for us to communicate with you (including, if you have consented, event information, product updates, and marketing communications). If we are shipping you products or marketing materials, then you may be asked to provide shipping related information, such as your telephone number, shipping address, and email address.

### Product Registration

When registering your product, you must provide your first name, last name, email address, type of product, serial number, date of purchase, proof of purchase, or other product-identifying information. We use this information to provide membership services and may be used to verify if you qualify for promotional events. If you choose not to provide this information, you will not be able to register products on the website; however, you may continue to use the products.

### Forum Registration

When registering for your forum account, you will be asked to provide your email, a user name, and a password. This information is used to allow you access to our forum under your account and to contact you about forum-related information, updates, and services.

### Non-Personal Information

We automatically collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit the website. We may use cookies and other technology to acquire or store this information. We collect this anonymous information so that we may better understand how people are using the website and to improve the overall quality of our users' online experience.

### Security

We do not collect your sensitive information such as credit card or debit card details. Although we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee non-sensitive information such as email addresses which you transmit to us over the internet are protected, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your information, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

### Cookies

Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information which are downloaded to your device when you visit our website. Cookies are used to make website navigation more efficient, remember your preferences and login session, and generally improve user experience.

Browsers typically allow cookies by default, but they can be configured to block some or all cookies, or to notify you before a cookie is about to be set on your browser. It is also possible to delete any cookies that may have been downloaded, simply by going into your browser settings. If you disable all cookies, this may prevent you using all of our services without interruption and taking full advantage of our website.

### Links to Other Websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. Nonetheless, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Aggregated Statistics

G.SKILL may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to our website. G.SKILL may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, these statistics do not contain any personally identifiable information.

### Analyzing Tools and Trackers

### Google Analytics

Our website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. You find more information concerning the treatment of user data by Google Analytics in Google's Privacy Policy: [https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2700409?hl=en](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2700409?hl=en)

In case of activation of the IP anonymization, Google will truncate/anonymize the last four numbers of the IP address for Member States of the European Union as well as for other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases, the full IP address is sent to and shortened by Google servers in the USA. On behalf of the website provider Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage to the website provider. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.

You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However, please note that if you do this, you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.

Furthermore, you can prevent collection by Google Analytics by clicking on the following link. This will install an opt-out cookie that will prevent future collection of your data on this part of the website: [Deactivate Google Analytics](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

### Youtube

Our website uses plugins of the Google-operated website YouTube. Provider of the website is YouTube, LLC, 901 Cherry Ave., San Bruno, CA 94066, USA. If you visit one of our website having a YouTube-plugin embedded, a connection to YouTube servers will be established. The YouTube server will then be submitted the information that you have visited our websites.

If you are logged on to your YouTube account, you enable YouTube to associate your browsing behavior with your personal profile. You may prevent this by logging out of YouTube.

You find further information concerning the treatment of user data in the Privacy Policy of YouTube under: [https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy)

### How Long Do We Keep Your Data?

We will only keep your data and information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes we collect it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

When we have fulfilled the purpose we collect your information for, we will either delete or anonymize it or, if this is not possible (for example, your information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any processing until deletion is possible.

### How Do We Share The Information We Collect?

As part of the services offered to you through our website, the information which you provide to us may be transferred to countries outside the European Union ("EU") and the United States ("US"). If we transfer your information outside of EU and US in this way, we will take steps to ensure that appropriate security measures are taken with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected as outlined in this Policy. If you use our services while you are outside EU, your information may be transferred outside EU and US in order to provide you with those services.

The information about you that we collect for a particular purpose will only be saved and used for that purpose, unless you have agreed to allow us to use it for some other purpose, as described in this Policy. Except as set forth in this Policy, we do not sell, trade, share, rent, or give away information concerning you to third parties.

### How Do We Protect Your Personal Data?

G.SKILL has taken appropriate technical and organizational measures to ensure that your personal data we have collected or will collect in the future is secure. For example, we have limited the number of people who have access to your personal data, by electronic security systems and authentication methods that guard against unauthorized access. As a reminder, G.SKILL provides links to third-party websites. These websites may not have the same privacy policies as G.SKILL. We take reasonable care in recommending these websites, but we are not responsible for their content or privacy policies. We urge users to read the privacy statement of a third-party website when leaving our Services and linking to a third-party website. We always use industry-standard technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data we receive. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you in connection with our website.

### Our Affiliates

Subject to applicable data protection law, we may share your information with legal entities that are directly or indirectly controlled by us or who share common control with us. These affiliates may use your personal information only in accordance with this Policy and for the purposes and reasons it sets out.

### CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)

Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:

* Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.
* Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.

If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to file the above-mentioned request, or exercise any of these rights, please see "[How to Contact Us](#howtocontactus)".

### GDPR Data Protection Rights

We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:

* **The right to access** – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.
* **The right to rectification** – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.
* **The right to erasure** – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.
* **The right to restrict processing** – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.
* **The right to object to processing** – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.
* **The right to data portability** – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.

If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.

### Children's Privacy

Our services are not intended for children under the age of 16, and as such, the website does not knowingly or intentionally collect, maintain, or disclose personal information from children under the age of 16. If you are under the age of 16, you may only use this website in the presence of a consenting parent or guardian.

As a parent or guardian, if you think that your child submitted personal identifiable information without your consent or by misrepresenting his or her age, you can request us to remove the information and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records. All such requests should include the same user name, password, and email address that your child submitted.

### Privacy Policy Updates and Changes

This Policy may be amended or updated from time to time to reflect the processing of personal data or changes in applicable law. We encourage you to read this Policy carefully, and to regularly check the website for information about revisions to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this website after any change in this Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

### Termination

G.SKILL may terminate your access to all or any portion of this Website at any time, with or without cause, with or without notice, effective immediately. If you wish to terminate your account, you may simply discontinue using this Website. Please refer to our Privacy Policy for any queries relating to your personal information after termination.

### APPLICABLE LAW AND JURISDICTION

By using any portion of this Website, you agree these Terms shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Taiwan, excluding its conflicts of law rules. You expressly agree that the exclusive jurisdiction for any claim or action arising out of or relating to these Terms of Use or your use of this Website shall be filed only in the courts located in Taipei, Taiwan, and you further agree and submit to the exercise of personal jurisdiction of such courts for the purpose of litigating any such claim or action between you and G.SKILL. Use of the Website is not authorized in any jurisdiction that does not give effect to all provisions of these Terms of the Policy, including without limitation, this section.

**If you have any questions about anything in this privacy policy or think that your personal data has been misused or mishandled, please contact our Data Privacy Officer ("DPO"):**

Data Privacy Officer  
Email: data.officer@gskill.com

### How to Contact Us

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, you can reach us at [privacy@gskill.com](mailto:privacy@gskill.com). We are located and registered at 8F #69 Dongxing Road, Xinyi District, Taipei City 11070, Taiwan.

Tel (International): +886-2-2766-7889  
Tel (USA): 1-833-2GSKILL (1-833-247-5455)
